introducing Microsoft Dynamics 365
business Central and its seamless
integration with
Shopify hi and welcome to Microsoft
Dynamics 365 business Central this video
highlights some of the benefits of using
business Central as the backend of your
shopi store business Central is a
powerful business management solution
that can help you run your daily
operations and do the finances for all
your Shopify stores and the brands you
sell in
them forget about expensive online
Commerce Integrations connecting
business Central to your Shopify store
is easy we'll guide you through the
process in just a few
steps business Central makes it easy to
keep inventory levels in your Shopify
store up to dat and can automatically
fulfill orders orders from your Shopify
shop flow directly into business Central
so you can focus your time on what's
important you can manage the details
about your products in business Central
and decide what to sell in your store
support for multiple locations lets you
optimize Warehouse processes to reduce
delivery times and address product and
business needs for example you might
want to use a specific warehouse for
handling returns revenue from your store
is automatically reflected in business
Central you get a 360° view of your
financials expenses and profits and
tools for reporting taxes to
authorities business Central also
integrates with productivity tools for
Microsoft Office for example you can use
teams to collaborate with colleagues on
orders use Outlook to communicate with
customers directly from business
Central or use one drive to store manage
and share
documents your Shopify store gives your
customers great shopping experiences
connecting your store to business
Central is great for your business
thanks for
watching